

■ lazicn378@gmail.com

Pančevo, Serbia

+381/65-368-3833

#### **Profile**

I'm a dedicated Full stack software developer, specializing mostly in C#, ASP.NET, Javascript, Angular, SQL Databases, and I also write PHP / Laravel code. Currently, I'm on final year on ICT College, Belgrade. For the past 3.5 years I'm actively learning programming. I'm a hardworking person, and I love working in team since I have 4 years of working experience outside of programming. I have finished 4 months internship for specialization in ASP.NET and Angular.

Currently I'm actively reading software engineering books such as "Head first design patterns" and "Clean Code" so that i keep improving my knowledge in software engineering and development.

# **Employment History**

Laravel Backend Developer, IT Development Solutions, Pančevo

April 2022 — May 2022

- Worked to meet client deadlines.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.
- Worked to assess competing websites in regards to content, database design, and performance.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and system requirements.

### Full-Stack Software Developer, Cycle d.o.o, Belgrade

September 2022 — Present

- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers.
- Successfully finished tasks based on client requirements.
- Successfully implemented software designs
- Full-stack flow, from UI components, communication with backend, creating backend logic and creating database design for specified problem.
- Using Dapper for ORM. Writing a lot of raw SQL queries.
- Using Azure Storage Account, Blob storage and Queues mostly.
- Working with Git, Azure DevOps, Agile

### Internships

Software Developer, Quadro Consulting, Belgrade

May 2022 — September 2022

Improving Angular and ASP.NET Core skills on 4 months internship. Mostly creating API, calling SQL procedures, using CQRS Pattern, SOLID principles and more.

### **Education**

ICT College, Belgrade

October 2019 — December 2022

#### Skills

C# .NET

ASP.NET

ASP.NET Core

ASP.NET API

JavaScript

Angular 2+

**SQL** Databases

SQL Server

**Entity Framework** 

Dapper ORM

Microsoft Azure

**SOLID** 

HTML5

CSS3

PHP

Laravel Framework

Bootstrap 4, 5

#### Links

Linkedin

**GitHub** 

### Languages

Serbian

English

German

Octifial

Department for Internet Technologies - Web Programming, software engineering

## **Courses**

C# Intermediate, Udemy

Javascript Intermediate, Udemy

HTL Leonding C# Course (2020/21), Rainer Stropek, YouTube

HTL Leonding Programming Course (2021/22), Rainer Stropek, YouTube